I heard that
سمعت ان
Loosen
تخفيف
Let go. I'm not healed yet
اتركه.  أنا لم أشفى بعد
Boy
ولد
It's the wine you hid me from
إنه النبيذ الذي أخفتني عنه
For florets
للزهور
As a former subordinate of the stockade leader
كمرؤوس سابق لزعيم الحاجز
I retrieved her missing wine
لقد استعدت النبيذ المفقود لها
It can be regarded as repaying her kindness
يمكن اعتباره بمثابة رد لطفها
Boy, you have a lot of courage
يا فتى، لديك الكثير من الشجاعة
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
I dare to steal my wife's wine
أجرؤ على سرقة نبيذ زوجتي
The consequences of boys provoking me
عواقب استفزاز الأولاد لي
The princess can't protect you from leaving
الأميرة لا تستطيع حمايتك من المغادرة
Stop scratching
توقف عن الخدش
In broad daylight, you smelly rascal
في وضح النهار، أيها الوغد ذو الرائحة الكريهة
Help me
ساعدني
Go in
أدخل
Secret order of obsidian
أمر سري من سبج
First
أولاً
Keep one's identity strictly confidential
الحفاظ على هوية المرء سرية للغاية
Violators die
المخالفين يموتون
Second
ثانية
One day hidden obsidian all day long hidden obsidian
يوم واحد سبج مخفي طوال اليوم سبج مخفي
Withdrawal dies
يموت الانسحاب
Third
ثالث
Do not harm the masses
لا تؤذي الجماهير
Violator dies
يموت المخالف
Dead and dead
ميت ومات
Die
موت
Do I still have a way to live? This
هل ما زال لدي طريقة للعيش؟  هذا
Are you going to sign or not
هل ستوقع أم لا؟
If you don't sign, you will die now
إذا لم توقع، سوف تموت الآن
Sign it and die worse
وقع عليه ويموت أسوأ
Tomorrow is the day of entering the palace
غدا هو يوم دخول القصر
How are you born to be on duty beside your highness
كيف ولدت لتكون في الخدمة بجانب سموك
Maybe
ربما
Be able to die
تكون قادرة على الموت
Thank you for your advice
شكرا لك على نصيحتك
You will be able to enter the palace soon
ستتمكن من دخول القصر قريبًا
Little Princess
اميرة صغيرة
I don't know if you remember me
لا أعرف إذا كنت تتذكرني
Stop, don't run, stop
توقف، لا تركض، توقف
Quickly
بسرعة
Stop
قف
Are you all right
هل انت بخير
Thank you
شكرًا لك
Come along with us
تعال معنا
Dad
أب
Take the princess away
خذ الأميرة بعيدا
If you want to find the little princess of that year,
إذا أردت العثور على الأميرة الصغيرة لذلك العام،
We can only start from Baozhu
لا يمكننا أن نبدأ إلا من باوزهو
Hair what Leng
شعر ما لينغ
Come and help me make up
تعال وساعدني في الماكياج
How can I wear makeup as a man
كيف يمكنني وضع المكياج كرجل
Be my man
كن رجلي
There are only two choices
هناك خياران فقط
Obedience and forced obedience
الطاعة والطاعة القسرية
Come here
تعال الى هنا
Don't say it
لا تقل ذلك
When you're not talking
عندما لا تتحدث
Kind of like a princess
نوع من مثل الأميرة
Why don't you melt it
لماذا لا تذوبه
Princess
أميرة
Enter the palace tomorrow
أدخل القصر غدا
Can you see it
هل تستطيع ان تراه
How many other princesses
كم عدد الأميرات الأخريات
Do you want to serve other princesses
هل تريدين خدمة الأميرات الأخريات؟
No, no, no, no
لا لا لا لا
I was born to be your man
لقد ولدت لأكون رجلك
Death is your dead man
الموت هو رجلك الميت
Little princess, in order to find you
الأميرة الصغيرة، من أجل العثور عليك
I am committed to Baozhu
أنا ملتزم باوزهو
You must wait for me
يجب أن تنتظرني
Quickening
تسارع
All right
حسنًا
Jin Jiu, I'll kill you
جين جيو، سأقتلك
Uncle Fu
العم فو
This nine-yang pill
هذه الحبة التسعة يانغ
Save the Princess
أنقذ الأميرة
Nine Yin Dan
تسعة يين دان
Leave it to Xiao Jiu
اترك الأمر لشياو جيو
Nine what Lord
تسعة ما يا رب
Jiuyang Dan saves the princess
جيويانغ دان ينقذ الأميرة
Nine Yin Dan for Xiao Jiu
تسعة يين دان لشياو جيو
Save the princess
انقاذ الاميرة
I see
أرى
I'll say it for the last time
سأقولها للمرة الأخيرة
Nine Yang Dan
تسعة يانغ دان
To the Princess
إلى الأميرة
Nine Yin Dan
تسعة يين دان
To Xiao Jiu
إلى شياو جيو
Xiao Jiu saved the princess
أنقذ Xiao Jiu الأميرة
I know. I know
أنا أعرف.  أنا أعرف
Jin Ba
لا أعرف
Nine Yin to Xiao Jiu
تسعة يين إلى شياو جيو
It's not right
انها ليست على حق
Nine Yin to Princess
تسعة يين للأميرة
Jiuyang to Xiao Jiu
جيويانغ إلى شياو جيو
It's all my fault that the old servant is deaf
كل هذا خطأي أن الخادم القديم أصم
Harm the little master and princess
إيذاء السيد والأميرة الصغيرة
Take the wrong medicine
تناول الدواء الخطأ
The old servant has few days to live
الخادم العجوز لديه أيام قليلة ليعيشها
Don't worry about the little master
لا تقلق بشأن السيد الصغير
And the princess
والأميرة
Relax
يستريح
Little Master
السيد الصغير
Little Princess
اميرة صغيرة
You must live
يجب أن تعيش
Wait till I come to you
انتظر حتى آتي إليك
Princess Wan'an
الأميرة وانان
The emperor has not yet arrived
الإمبراطور لم يصل بعد
Please ask the princess to meet the other princesses first
من فضلك اطلب من الأميرة مقابلة الأميرات الأخريات أولاً
Take a short rest
خذ استراحة قصيرة
Come on, come on, you go
هيا، هيا، اذهب
Yes
نعم
I don't want to play with them
لا أريد أن ألعب معهم
Let's wait in the garden
دعونا ننتظر في الحديقة
Princess
أميرة
Let's play hide-and-seek
هيا نلعب الغميضة
If you find me,
إذا وجدت لي،
We'll just
حسنا اذا
Interesting, interesting
مثيرة للاهتمام ومثيرة للاهتمام
Then let's get started
ثم دعونا نبدأ
Good
جيد
Ninety-nine
تسع وتسعون
Ninety-eight
ثمانية و تسعون
Ninety-seven
سبعة وتسعون
Ninety-six
ستة و تسعون
Ninety-five
خمسة وتسعون
Little princess, I'm coming
أيتها الأميرة الصغيرة، أنا قادمة
Ninety-four
اربعة وتسعون
Ninety-three
ثلاثة و تسعون
Ninety-two
إثنان وتسعون
Sample, I see what tricks you have
عينة، وأرى ما هي الحيل لديك
You see
هل ترى
Which one is the little princess
أي واحدة هي الأميرة الصغيرة
Got it
فهمتها
I'm pregnant with your baby
أنا حامل بطفلك
And you seduced my sister
وأنت أغوي أختي
I can't believe you are pregnant with my child
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنك حامل بطفلي
Sister Huang
الأخت هوانغ
Don't blame me for being cruel
لا تلومني لكوني قاسية
This evil seed
هذه البذرة الشريرة
I have to remove it for you
لا بد لي من إزالته بالنسبة لك